Guide to the Edward J. McCluskey Papers SC1112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Administrative files
  - McClure, Robert M., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Luckham, David, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - LOSQ, Jacques, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Kunii, Tosiyasu L., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Koren, Israel, 1977-1978, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Linvill, John G., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Kachukhashvili, George S., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Kanuma, Akira, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Karpovsky, Mark, 1978, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Kautz, Willaim H., 1977 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Khakbaz, Javad, 1980, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Khodadad-M., Behzad, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Kim, Yong-Deak, 1975, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - King, H.L., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Ishizuka, Okihiko, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Hirose, Fumiyasu, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Hodges, David A., 1973, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Holm, Julia, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Hong. Se June, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Hronicek, Richard Arthur, 1978 July (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Hsiao, Man-Tung Tony, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Hughes, Joe, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Army, Final Report, 1986 Jan. (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - ARO Propsal - Computer Systems Reliability and Failure Prediction, 1988 March 31, 1985 April 1 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Reg. for Evaluation, 1975, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - ARO Proposal - Measurement & Statistical Modeling of Computer Reliability as Affected by System Activity, 1983 April 1-1985 March 31 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - ARO Proposa; - The Measurement and Statistical Modeling of Reliability as Affected by Systrem Activity, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Progress Report No. 4, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - ARO Proposal - Design of Reliable Small Scale Digital Systems: Low Cost Techniques for Fault-Tolerance and Maintainability SEL 2-74, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - ARMY - Study of Very High Speed Integrated Circuit and Data (See Naval Electronic Systems Command Original), 1980 July (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - ARO Proposal - An Investigation of Gracefully Computing Sys: Using Perform & Cost-Related Reliability Measures SEL 3-78, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Propsal Sel 3-78, "An Investigation of Gracefully Degrading Computing Systems: Evaluation Using Performance and Cost-Related Reliabilty Measures, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - AROD Proposal - Reliabilty Evaluation of Computer Systems: Analytical Modeling - SEL 37-76, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous and Contract Info., 1975 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - JSEP Proposal - Extension of Contract N00014-75-C-0601 SEL 39-76, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - JSEP Proposal - Computer Architecture, 1976 Sept. (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - RATS 385A, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - RATS, 2004 Fall (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - RATS, 2007 Spring (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - RATS, 2008 Spring (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - 385A, 2007 Jan.-March (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - RATS, 2007 Fall (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - RATS, 2008 Winter (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Ken Thesis (blank Folder_, undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - RATS, 2005 June (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - RATS, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - CIS Adbisory Committee Meeting, 1998 April 22 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - SouthCon, 1985 March (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - IEEE Trans. on Computers, Vol. C-33, #8, J. Khakbaz & E.J. McCluskey - Self-testing Embedded Parity Checkers, 1984 Aug. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Encoder and Totally Self-Checking Error Detector Design of Autonomous Linear Feedback Shift Registers, 1983 Nov. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Test Generation and Fault Diagnosis for Multiple Faults in Combinational Circuits, 1983 Nov. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Concurrent Fault Detection Using a Watchdog Processor and Assertions, 1983 Nov. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - IEEE TC - Special Issue on Fault - Tolerant Computing, Folder No. 3, 1984 June (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - IEEE Trans. on Computers, vol. C-33, No. 8, Khakbaz - A Testable PLA Design with Low Overhead & high Faullt Converage, 1984 Aug. 8 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Eighteenth Annual Asilomar Conference on Circuits, Systems and Computers Pacific Grive, California, 1984 Nov. 5-7 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Ate Silicon valley Conference San Mateo, California, 1984 April 10-12 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Built-In Self Test Workshop, Kiawah Island, Charleston, South Carolina, 1984 Feb. 28-March 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The 11th Annual Int'l Symposium on Computer Architecture, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1984 June 4-7 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - IEEETC, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - IEEETC, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - D&T - EJMc845-A Procedure for Testing BIT-Sliced Microprocessor by Suresh Rai and Rajiv Jain (Blank Folder), undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - IEEE Design & Test of Computers Withdrawn Manuscripts (Blank Folder), undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - A Design for Testability Scan techniques, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - D&T - EJMc844, test Software: Uses, Methods and Trends by Gordon W. Plunkett and Kuang-Wei Chiang, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - IEEE Design & Test, Paper No. EJMc843 Lefas, C.C. and E.T. Powner, Data Compression Ate Design, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - IEEE Design & Test - Paper EJMc 842 Su, S.Y.H. and T. Lin, Functional Testing Techniques for Digital LSI/VLSI, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - IEEE Design & Test - Paper EJMc 841 Malaiya, Y.K. and R. Narayannaswamy Modeling & Testing for Timing Faults in Synchronous Sequential VLSI, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - IEEED&T EJMc 852 - Kleeman, L. & A. Cantoni, Metastable Behavior & Digital System Reliability, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - IEEE D&T Ed. Byrd Reviews: Hlawickzka, Dr. Andrzej "Binary Implemented Exhaustive testing", 1985 April (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - IEEED&T EJMc 851-Hlawiczka, A., Binary Implemented Exhaustive testing of Multi-Valued Logic Networks, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - R. Buhler, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Mrs. H.R., 1966-1967, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - T 17, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - SAGE/ Technical Memorandum, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Procedures & Operations Manual SAGE Computer Support Group, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Control Data 3600, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - VTS, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - VTS, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - International Test Conference, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - International Test Conference, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Y. Zorian TECS Reviews, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - FFCM (Field-Programmable Computing Machines) Submissions, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - FTCS Submissions, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - VTS, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - IDDQ, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - ICCAD (International Conference on Computer Aided Design) Submissions, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - ITC Submissions, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - SMC Submission, 1998 (Box not specified, Folder 12)
  - VLSI Design Submission, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - VTS, 1998 April 26-30 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - ICCAD Submissions, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - ITC Submissions, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - IDDQ Submissions, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - ITSW Submissions, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - VTS Submissions, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - ITC Submissions, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - ITSW Abstracts, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - HLDVTW (High Level Design Validation and Test Workshop), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - IDDQ Workshop, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - CRC Open House, 1996 May 10 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - ITSW Submissions, 1996 May 6-8 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Chang - Quantitative Analysis of Very-Low-Voltage Testing, 1996 Apr. 28-May 1 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Norwood - Synthesis for Scan and Scan Chain Ordering, 1996 April 28- May 1 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Touba - Applying Two-Pattern Tests Using Scan-Mapping, 1996 April 28- May 1 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Touba - Test Point Insertion Based on Path Tracing, 1996 April 28- May 1 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Spice 2 - Homework, Solutions, Labs, Quizzes & Final, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Touba - Logic Synthesis of Multilevel Circuits with Concurrent Error Detention - Touba & EJM, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Saxena - Linear Complexity Assertions for Sorting Algorithms - Saxena & EJM, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Papers, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Saxena - Parallel Signature Analysis Design with Counds on Aliasing - Saxena & EJM, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Measurement & Statistical Modeling, 1984 May (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Aro - The measurement & Statistical Modeling of Computer Reliability as Affected by System Activity, 1983 September (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Very-High Speed Integrated Circuit, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - AROD Proposal - Abstract, not dated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - AROD Progress Reports, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - AROD - Monthly and Interim Reports, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Bridging & Stuck-at Faults, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Faults Dominance in Combinational Circuits, 1970 August (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - AROD - Contract and Modifications, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - AROD Reports, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - MSM, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - ARO, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - CS 311, 1973 Spring (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - First Annual VHSIC Program Review - Arlington Virginia, 1981 June 15-19 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - AROD, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - ARO Report, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - AROD Proposal, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - ARO Report, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - RKI Project Summary, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - AROD Contract - Measurement and Statistical Modeling, 1982 April 1 - 1984 March 31 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - AROD - Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - AROD - The measurement and statistical Modeling of Computer Reliability as affected by System Activity, 1980 October 1 - 1983 September 30 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - AROD - Technical Report Records, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - AROD VHSIC Project, 1980 September 25 - 1983 September 24 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - AROD - The measurement and statistical Modeling of Computer Reliability as affected by System Activity, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - AROD - The measurement and statistical Modeling of Computer Reliability as affected by System Activity, 1981 October 1 - 1984 November 30 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Patent, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - LUMEN - Intellectual property services - Patent Info, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Patent - Duty to Disclose Reminder, 2001 October 1 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Items for Dean's Report, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - CS Strategic Plan, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Malaiya Bridge Fits, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Saxena, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Steve - Bridging Fault Results, 1985 November 25 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - TPG - Bottorff, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Photos, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - IEEE Computer Society Award, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Annual President's Report (Dean's Report), 1974-1990 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Army - Study of Very High Speed Integrated Circuit (VHSIC Phase 3) and Data, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Army - Study of Very High Speed Integrated Circuit (VHSIC Phase 3) and Data, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - DARPA Contract MDA General Purpose VLSA-Based Multiprocessor Design and Implementation, 1983 July 1- 1986 June 30 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - CIS Proposal - Modelling Failure Modes in MOS Technology, 1985 May (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - INTNSF Proposal - Studies on Logic Design of VLSI Digital Circuits with high Reliability, 1980 January - 1981 December (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - NASA NAG 2-246, Development of a Flights Software Testing Methodology - Final Report, 1965 September (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - NASA-AMES - Development of an Aviation Software Testing Methodology, Project 2DPN580, 1983 August 1 - 1985 September 30 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - NASA-AMES Personal - Development of an Aviation Software Testing Methodology, 1983 August 1 - 1985 September 30 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - NASA-Langley Grant, 1976 December (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - NASA Official Papers, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - NASA Proposal- Enumeration of the Critical Fault Patterns in the Fault - Tolerant Computer Systems, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - APL 360 Instructions for Operation, 1966 November (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Columbia University Project Files, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Design Automation: Current Techniques and Applications - Chapters 6-7, 1976 July (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Army - Study of Very High Speed Integrated Circuit (VHSIC Phase 3) - Technical Report, 1982 March (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - NASA-Langley Research Center - Critical Fault Pattern Determination in Fault-Tolerant Computer Systems, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Intercommunication of processors and memory, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Willner - Design of the B1700, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Rice and Smith - von Neumann computing systems, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - CS 311, 1971 Spring (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Various Contracts and Technical Reports, 1975-1984 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Army - Study of very high speed integrated circuits (VHSIC-Phase 3) and data, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Army - Study of very high speed integrated circuits (VHSIC-Phase 3) and data, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - LMSC, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Design Automation: Current Techniques and Applications - Chapters 1-3, 1976 July (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Design Automation: Current Techniques and Applications - Chapters 4-5, 1976 July (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Design Automation: Current Techniques and Application - Chapters 8-9, 1976 July (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - B 5000 - Design of the System, 1961 May (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - CS 311/ EE 482, 1977 Autumn (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - CS 311 Class Notes, 1977 Autumn (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - CS 311 Instructor Sets, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Computer Task Force, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - CS 311, 1977 Fall (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Logic and Switching, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Numerical Aerodynamic Simulation Facility Feasibility Study - Final Report, 1979 March (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Control Data 6000 Computer Systems Reference Manual, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Programming Notes and Texts, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Control Data 6600 Computer System Reference Manual, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Control Data 6400/6500/6600 Computer Systems Reference Manual, 1967 May (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Control Data 6400/6600 Computer Systems Reference Manual, 1966 September (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 6400 Central Processor Training Manual, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - IBM System 370 Model 145 Functional Characteristics Manual, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - IBM System 370 Model 145 Operating Procedures Manual, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - UNIBUS Interface Manual, 1971 December (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - CS 311 - CRAY 1, 1978 October (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - CS 311 Address Mem Hier, 1978 October (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Conference Papers, 1973 March (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - AHPL, 1974 April (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - History, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Berkeley Computer Corp., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Conferences on Computer Science in EE Education, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - CS 231, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - OYOC Program, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Bell Telephone, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - File - IEEE Computer Society, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - CS 311, 1971 July (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Stat 217, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - CODD, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - IBM Palo Alto Scientific Center Technical Report, 1973 August (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Osterby, 1975 March (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Bubble Ladder for Information Processing, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - EE 381 Handouts-Copies, 1986 Autumn (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Lecture Notes 1965-67, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Relay Book - Sections 1-12 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - JSEP (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - IBM Equipment Order (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Computer Science Committee (CSC) Appointments (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Rel & Moint - HA (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - MIND - Medical Information Network Development, 1974 Apr 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Computer Science Department, 1962-1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Semiconductors Lecture Notes (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Counters Lecture Notes (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Logics Lecture Notes (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Diagrams/ Drawings (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Error Control & Detection in Input/Output (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Computer Science Department & Newspapers (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Transfer Circuit Drawings, 1970s (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - SLAC & Carnegie-Mellon Reports - Part 1, 1970-1978 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - SLAC & Carnegie-Mellon Reports - Part 2, 1970-1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Computer Science Department - CS Notes & Diagrams, 1970-1978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Kyoto University, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - EQ B316/ E172 Notes (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Archives - Computer Science Education (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Computer Science Labatory - Stanford (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Testing, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - CS311, 1964-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Wallace - A Suggestion for a Fast Multiplier, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Multiplication, 1973-1979 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - EE 281, 1968 Fall (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - CS 311 Handouts, 1979 Fall (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - EE 381-CS 211 Lecture Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - APL 360, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - CS 311 Homework and Papers, 1971-1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - J.A. Rajchman, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Memory, 1972-1977 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - SR Adders, 1972-1978 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - FP11-C Floating-point processor Maintence Manual, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - CS 311, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Digital Test Principles Tutorial #1, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Digital Test Principles Tutorial #2 & #10, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Digital Test Principles Tutorial #5 & #13, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Digital Test Principles Tutorial #1 - Notes, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - LSI-11 WCS User's Guide, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Amdahl Machine Reference Manual, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Burroughs B 5500 Information Processing Systems Reference Manual, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - 6600 Central Processor - Volume II Functional Units, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Control Data 6400-6600 Computer Systems Reference Manual, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - On the Design of a Very High-Speed Computer, 1957 October (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Control Data 7600 Computer System - Preliminary System Description, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Intel - The Semiconductor Memory Book, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Parallel 300, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Intel 432 Reference Manual, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - The MC4006 Decoders, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Agilent (Participation agreement with S.U.), 2004 August (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - BAST, 1990-2003 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - BAST, 1990-2003 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - List of Accounts, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - CISCO, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - DARPA, 1997-2006 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ROAR Files, 1997-2001 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - DARPA - Quickturn, 1997-2006 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ROAR Kick off Meeting, 1998 February 23 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - DARPA Project Summaries, 1997-2006 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Hewlett Packard - Agilent, 1989-2002 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Intel Gift - CRC, 2006 December (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Intel Gift - CRC, 2005 December (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Intel Gifts, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Intel Financial Pages, 2003 February 7 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Intel, 1991-1998 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Intel Grant - Work Stations, 2002 Summer (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Intel W-9 Request, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Financials that were in the Intel File, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Budget Proposal - Intel, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - JPL, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - LSI Logic Gift Award, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Testing Digital Logic LSI, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - LSI Expenses, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - LSI Award Notice, 2003 November (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Duplicate Copies - LSI, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Logic Vision Research Agreement, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - LSI Logic Contract, 1996-1998 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - LSI Amendment, 2003 August 5 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - LSI Logic Contract # 16517, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - LSI Logic Proposals, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - LSI Logic Proposal, 1999-2001 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - LSI Logic Meeting Minutes, 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - LSI Logic, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - NSF Award Closeout Notification, 2006 December (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - NSF QABFT Estimate for Extension, 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - NSF Proposal, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Instructions-Preparing NSF Proposals, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - NSF extension, 2004 July 2 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - NSF Copyright Permission, 2004 February (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - NSF Annual Report, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - NSF Annual Report, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - NSF Proposal, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - NSF, 2001 April 1 - 2004 March 31 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - nVidia Gift, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - NVidia NDA Blank Forms, undated (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - NVidia Budget, 2003 April (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - NVidia Gift Award-Signed Document, 2003 November 13 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - NVidia Gift Award Letter, 2003 May (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - NVidia NDA's - Signed, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - BAST Workshop Financial Reports, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - XiLinx Agreement, 2002 October (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - XiLinx Final Report, 2003 December (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - XiLinx, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Xilinx Proposal, 2000-2003 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - SRC Contract Amendment, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - SRC 3 Year Budget, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - SRC Award, 2004 March 8 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - SRC Studnet Forms - original, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - SRC Contract, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Form 6, 2004 February (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - SRC Long False Paths Letters - Accept., 2004 January 8 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - SRC Web Account, 2004 February (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - SRC Proposal, 2003 December 1 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - SRC, 2000 October 1 - 2003 September 30 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - SRC New Acct #, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - SRC Award Notice, 2004 March 11 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - SRC Student Information, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - SRC - FTP Files, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Tektronix, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Renew Maintenance Contact, 1987 December (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - Tektronics Contribution, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Stanford Electronics Laboratory, 1961 Jan.1-March 31 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Electronics Labs, 1961 Oct.-1962 Jan. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Laboratories, 1962 April-July (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - RATs, 2007-2008 Summer (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - RATs, 2003 Sumer (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Logic Vision Logic BIST (Hong), 2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - BAST, 2003 Feb. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Handout #19, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Philips NDA, 2002 Oct. 31 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - RATs Ant, 2002 Jan. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - RATs, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - EE Faculty Retreat, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Bob Madge, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - RATs, 2001 Summer (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - RATs, 2001 Winter (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - EE, 2000 Nov. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - RATs 385A, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University Telephone System, 1985 Dec. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Japan Prize News (American and Japanese Scientists names as Laureates", 1995 Jan. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - RATs Spoo, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - ELF Vu, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Murphy Focls Elf, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - RATs, 2000 Fall (Box 30, Folder 23)